Hello, I am Honoka Hirao. I am Rina Watanabe. I am Nanami Konishi. I am Rina Shimizu. I am Haruka Yamashita.
Isn't this a rare member? It's very rare. Today, I'd like to include some of my own words in this project.
I brought this card game that I love to play with everyone.
The game is Tomato Mato. It's a Tomato Mato game. Simply put, it's a game where you say a word quickly and repeat it over and over again.
Wow, I'm good at it! I'm good at it. I'm good at it.
Tomato Mato is played with 5 kinds of cards and dice with a roll of up to 3.
The cards are flipped from the deck according to the roll of the dice,
The cards in the deck are read out like a rapid speech.
The same thing is repeated,
If a player fails, the other player who failed is chosen,
If someone fails, the other players point to the card they want.
If no one else fails, the player gets the card.
The winner is the one who can make more tomatoes with the cards he or she has won.
What's that box in the back?
This is the box. We have a special rule this time. If you can't say a word, you will be punished by drawing one of the words from this box.
We have thought of about three for each person and put them in the box.
Who wrote this? What did you write?
Tell us!
You said you just want to have fun.
That's right.
I'll do my best.
Then I'll roll the dice first.
I thought the dice were tomatoes.
Nice.
You gave me a nice.
Yay!
The system is that I draw the dice and the person to my left says.
I draw and I say it.
That's right. Haruharu because it's the first time.
Then I'll draw.
Yes, the first pitch.
It's important.
One tomato.
Oh!
One tomato.1 Tomato.
Gentle gentle.
You put one in.
For a first.
You're gonna do this in less than three seconds?
Yes. I thought it was too slow.
I see.
What's that? The hard part?
Here we go. Ready?
Okay.
All right!
I took care of this.
That's the easiest one.
Here we go.
Here we go. Ready.
Tomatoes.
Oh!
A reverse card.
Reverse.
It's a reverse card.
Two cards.
Here we go.
Interesting.
Ready.
Matoma matoma.
Matoma.
Yes chosen.
It wasn't wrong.
I made a mistake.
It's three cards. It's a battle. You take the one you want with this.
Whoever has the most tomatoes in the end wins, so it's OK if there are lots of tomatoes in the combination.
You should really pick the tomatoes. Actually, the goal was one tomato.
You want a tomato because it will be completed. In fact, you should choose tomatoes.
The cat will win. I'll tell you right away. Here we go.
Ready?
It's totally fine. Three kamets, three kamets.
This is the discard, and this one stays. So, special rules. This is the discard, and this remains the same. So, special rules.
I wonder if everyone is following? The rules. Do you understand? I forgot.
I thought I forgot.
Shake it, shake it.
Pull. It's about two of a person's face. You can hit yourself, you know.
I see. That's true.
That's the funniest story I've heard recently. It's hard.
Is that what I wrote? Maybe it was me.
I forgot. But that's okay.
It's easy.
Okay, let's talk about Rio and Rio's way of talking.
The way they talk.
I always laugh.
Eh.
Usually.
Usual.
It's normal.
What's the timing?
Seriously, Rio, you've seen her before. We've all seen it.
The moment he turns off, he becomes a hot doraemon.
That's right.
It's funny how he always talks in a weird way.
You are more like Doraemon, aren't you, with your clothes?
That's for sure.
Indeed.
No, Dorami.
Doraemon.
Oh.
That's great.
Ponica?
One more time.
One more time, that's how many.
Here we go. Here we go.
Here we go.
Another one.
So sweet.
Okay, I'm going.
Okay.
Mina-chan.
Mina-chan, I'm going.
Ready.
Tomato.
Oh, no.
Yes.
Now that's a voice.
Don't say it like that.
I don't know.
Tomato.
I'm going to say it slowly.
Did you get it?
Maybe that's what the song is about.
Ready?
Ready.
Tomato.
Oh, no.
It's totally impossible.
What?
Where?
They're both covered.
Well, maybe I'll buy some more Izura.
It's, uh, such-and-such.
What?
Me?
Punishment, punishment.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Uh-oh.
Sorry, sorry.
Oh, punishment.
Oh, one time.
One time.
Yay.
Yay!
I really did it.
Come in, Sakkirina-chan.
Oh, it's a boat.
It's so big.
Imitation
Imitating the person to the left.
There's only the person on the left.
That's hard to do.
It's easy.
Did you find it?
I think I can do it.
Rina, I found a silver one for the race.
She'll definitely tell us about the bento.
You're gonna have to feed me.
You're early.
You'll be the first to see it, right?
Whenever I find out what my classmates like, I want to tell them.
Like, "This is Haruharu's favorite.
Or Rinachi's silver salmon.
I know what everyone likes.
It's about time.
I want to add one more.
Here we go.
Two.
It's going up. It's going up, it's going up, it's going up.
I'm scared. I'm scared. It's been a long time.
Here we go.
Matato-Matato
That's only two.
Two more. Two more.
This one's opposite.
Clump together, clump together, clump together, clump together.
That's out.
Masha-masha-masha.
That was a mistake.
It's a mistake.
I don't know what to do.
Shall I point again?
Okay.
Yay!
Tomato, tomato, tomato!
I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it!
Okay, next.
We have a game for you... a game for you...
Thank you very much.
It's going down pretty fast.
I thought it was going to be a long game.
Speed it up.
Shinburi Chan
Ahhhh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'm going to go say boo boo, and I'm going to go say boo boo, and I'm going to go say boo boo, and I'm going to go say boo boo!
Not too many colors, too good Seller's break, here you go
Oh, I've got results!
Oh, yeah, your hard work was out of the intertwino bar!
Igaishimu, you're talking about the great outdoors
4 Force green and 3 candy court hmmm...
Oh, my gosh!
Here's the video!
Here we go!
Nitomato
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
Here we go!
Seino
Matomato tower
I give up, I give up
I can't go on at all I can't go on at all.
Even by myself.
I'm done.
But if it's less than three seconds, I can look at it for a second and then start saying it.
I can start saying...
I'll just look at it for a second and then I'll start saying it.
Or you can say "tomato" or "tomato tomato.
Okay, I'll point again.
Ready?
See?
I got four.
Four people didn't get it.
This is the last game.
I'll see you this way, please.
Except for Assembly, really.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, here comes Semburi, for me.
Ta-da!
What do you think?
Clenic acid drink.
I've never heard of it.
It's so acidic.
It's not a clenic acid drink.
It's good for you.
I'm not sure yet.
I'm curious about this.
I'm curious.
Can I just smell it?
Let's start with the look and smell.
I'll have the clenic acid drink.
It doesn't smell at all!
Oh, really?
No, no, no.
It's okay. It's okay.
Here we go.
Looks delicious.
Bon appétit.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Oh! That's great! But it's a lot!
You know what?
It tastes like a vitamin C supplement dissolved in water.
Give me 3, Mr. Yamashita!
It's been far away my lucky number 2!
Smell...
Tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes...
This is the fastest and smoothest I've ever had!
What I'm looking for is...
Here we go!
All right.
Tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes...
Oh, look out!
Oh, my God.
Just in time.
Rina, hang in there.
Here we go.
Ready?
Tomato, tomato, tomato, tomato.
Oh!
You're safe.
You're so sweet.
I really won't forget.
You still did.
Yes, I have.
That's great.
Yes, sir.
Tomato, tomato, tomato, tomato, tomato, tomato.
Oh, my God.
You're good.
You said it.
Wait a minute.
Watch out!
First class Haruharu believe in yourself
Sempreture
Woah, watch out! Wooo dangerous
Tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes, tomatoes
That was a lot.
Did you say mama-mama?
That's out.
That was close.
Don't let up.
That was the last one, I swear.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
Oh, it's tomatoes?
That's what I meant.
On the contrary.
It's a mind game, isn't it?
Ta-da!
Four and...
Four and good.
Four doors.
Sempreture.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh, my God.
I've only done stretches today.
I don't know.
It's odorless.
Yes, it's odorless.
Cheers!
Look at this.
Oh, but it tastes so much better than the last one.
I'm good with sour.
No, you're not.
The last one.
My mind can't speak. My heart can't speak.
I can't speak.
I still can't speak.
No, I can't.
It's in my throat. It stays in your throat.
This place was different.
Oh, no.
Well...
Spring
That's why...
How many times have I done this?
Three.
Two.
That's good.
Right away.
It's me, isn't it?
Seino
Maima and Maima and Maima
I'm a member.
It was stable.
Here we go!
That's it!
Momma and momma...
What's that?
What?
Oh, no.
Work with gusto
Out
Out.
Yes!
Yeah!
Yay!
Oh, sorry.
I got you.
I got it.
I got it! I got it!
I got it! I got it! I got it!
You got it.
And this one.
Okay, here we go.
What the fuck were you doing?
Punishment. game played as a form of punishment
Oh, the penalty game.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I forgot.
All right, all right, all right.
Let's get ready.
There's nothing here.
Ready?
Let's go.
It's a pun.
Oh!
There's a pun master here.
Let's see how good you are.
Can you use tomatoes?
Yes, sir.
Tomato pun.
But it doesn't sound right.
I don't get it.
Okay, okay.
You can do it.
Amazing.
I can do it!
Okay, I'll get the camera.
Okay.
Until Konishi-san's pun.
Three.
Three... two... one...
One.
Let's stop before the tomatoes.
Oh, wow.
I'm at 99. Thank you very much.
Ninety-nine, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99.
Three more to go. I want you to pull three and give them all a glass of wine, please.
I'd like you to drink a little bit of that.I'd like you to take a drink.
Okay. - 321.
Three, three, three, three, three, three...
I'm sorry. Why didn't I get a three?
I wanted to make 3. I'll go.
Ready?
With tomatoes...
Yuukata, you're late...
Not too late?
I'm afraid you're out.
Out, out, out...
You did it!
So cute!
Here you go.
Meow.
Coin.
Monomaniac.
Everyone wants to see it, don't they?
Then tell me who you want to see.
That's how I feel.
You're thinking about it.
Okay, Tamaki Ishizuka.
Here it is!
Rina-chan to Tamaki Ishizuka.
Nyan-nay, I want to drink a cola!
Arina, go get me a Coke.
Hey, I made her say "nyan" legally!
So cute!
It's true... it means he's using me as his errand boy.
Tama-hara-tama-hara.
I've seen it before.
I have.
They make me do it over and over... card selection.
I guess so.
I don't know.
Let's see what you got.
Okay, please. Okay, please.
C'est la vie tomato
All right.
And here's the lid.
Last one.
One more card to go, and then you can pull it back.
That's right.
Last one.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, sir.
Matoma.
That was a little bit late.
A little bit late.
For three cards.
It was about five seconds too late.
Yes, sir.
Oh, wow.
Do it.
Here we go.
Let's go!
One more pull.
No, you can't.
It's no good.
What is it?
Mr. Kuen drink
I knew it!
Here it comes.
Okay, here we go.
It's a commercial for Mr. Quen.
Yes, sir.
There's Mr. Kuen here.
Cheers.
I like it.
Cheers! Come on!
Woo.
Good.
Cute!
Ah!
Hmm?
Ooh.
Amazing.
Oh, no!
It's a terrible, terrible commercial.
Oh, no.
It makes me sad.
Yes, sir.
Yes
All the cards are gone.
The results are in.
The number of tomatoes.
Yes, sir.
Tomatoes. Tomatoes. Tomatoes.
Tomato. Tomato. Tomato.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Let's start with Haruka.
Yes, ma'am.
Zero tomatoes
I... I...
Me.
Yes, ma'am.
Four tomatoes.
That's great.
Best record. Highest record.
It was definitely 4.
Four.
Okay, then.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Okay.
One tomato.
Oh.
I have three tomatoes.
Three tomatoes.
Surprise, surprise, surprise.
Actually
Actually...
The last one
Game Master
Game master.
Yes, sir.
One. Two.
Five tomatoes.
Oh!
One, two.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Good, good, good.
That's a winner.
That's what I'm talking about.
Game Master
weren't there
significAS
I'll bring you some more interesting cards. I'd like to bring something that Haruharu seems to be good at.
Please, it'll be fun. Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel and rate us! Bye bye!
Let's go for it!
So the two of you haven't taken your citric acid yet. So, two of us haven't taken the citric acid yet.
We're just trying to avoid water.
Cheers.
No expression.
Goku, Goku, Goku.
That's great!
Hey Konishi
I don't know...
It's delicious.
I was drinking too.
It was fine.
It reminded me of ice water.
And the heart.
I feel like I lost weight.